[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Hello There]
[أهلاً بك]
[Episode 7]
[الحلقة 7]
What?
لما؟
I have to pull weeds
لا بد لي من سحب الأعشاب الضارة
for these black radishes?
لهذه الفجل الأسود؟
Fine. I'll do it.
بخير.  سأفعل ذلك.
I definitely won't need your help this time.
بالتأكيد لن أحتاج إلى مساعدتك هذه المرة.
Watch out!
احذر!
I didn't fall.
أنا لم أسقط.
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Why are you lying on the floor?
لماذا ترقد على الأرض؟
I'll be kind.
سأكون لطيفا.
Let me help you.
دعني اساعدك.
Here.
هنا.
I'm really tired today.
أنا متعب حقًا اليوم.
Then have a good rest.
ثم احصل على قسط جيد من الراحة.
We'll talk about the rest tomorrow.
سنتحدث عن الباقي غدا.
All right.
حسنا.
The starry sky is so beautiful.
السماء المرصعة بالنجوم جميلة جدا.
Sitting quietly like this,
يجلس بهدوء مثل هذا ،
it feels so great to be carefree.
إنه شعور رائع أن تكون هادئًا.
If you like it, then be it.
إذا كنت ترغب في ذلك ، فليكن.
It's not that easy.
الأمر ليس بهذه السهولة.
I still have a blood vessel issue to solve.
لا يزال لدي مشكلة في الأوعية الدموية لحلها.
Let's forget it.
دعونا ننسى ذلك.
I'll seize every happy day while I can.
سأغتنم كل يوم سعيد بينما أستطيع.
Li Chengxi,
لي تشنغسي ،
leave me a room in Xuanqi Mountain.
اترك لي غرفة في جبل Xuanqi.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll leave you a room.
سأترك لك غرفة.
You're really a good friend. Very good.
أنت حقا صديق جيد.  حسن جدا.
Morning.
صباح.
I slept so well last night.
لقد نمت جيدًا الليلة الماضية.
You slept well?
لقد نمت جيدا؟
I think you were just exhausted
أعتقد أنك كنت منهكًا للتو
and passed out.
وأغمي عليه.
My brother is famous for
أخي مشهور ب
his strict supervision in Xuanqi Mountain.
إشرافه الصارم في جبل Xuanqi.
You must have been tortured hard
لابد أنك تعرضت للتعذيب الشديد
by my brother yesterday.
من أخي أمس.
No. Yesterday your brother...
رقم أمس أخوك ...
Young Master!
المعلم الصغير!
Bad news!
اخبار سيئة!
The formation down the mountain was broken.
تم كسر التكوين أسفل الجبل.
A dozen of martial artists broke in.
اقتحم عشرات من فناني الدفاع عن النفس.
They were shouting and want us to hand over the Wushan.
كانوا يصرخون ويريدون منا تسليم ووشان.
What?
لما؟
They came so soon.
جاؤوا قريبا جدا.
How dare they break into my mountain?
كيف يجرؤون على اقتحام جبلي؟
Their heads can be offerings to worship my sword.
يمكن أن تكون رؤوسهم قرابين لعبادة سيفي.
Wait.
انتظر.
Don't act rashly.
لا تتصرف بتهور.
Let's take a look first.
دعونا نلقي نظرة أولاً.
What a stupid maze!
يا لها من متاهة غبية!
It made us a mess!
لقد جعلتنا في حالة من الفوضى!
I must get the Wushan today!
يجب أن أحصل على Wushan اليوم!
Yes.
نعم.
The Double Demons of Xuanqi Mountain harm the martial arts circle
تضر الشياطين المزدوجة لجبل Xuanqi بدائرة فنون الدفاع عن النفس
and monopolize the Wushan.
وتحتكر منطقة ووشان.
Everyone wants them to be executed.
الكل يريد أن يتم إعدامهم.
Brothers, let's go!
أيها الإخوة ، دعنا نذهب!
Crush Xuanqi Mountain!
سحق جبل Xuanqi!
Looks like it's getting interesting.
يبدو أنه أصبح ممتعًا.
Who was shouting about crushing Xuanqi Mountain?
من كان يصرخ بشأن سحق جبل شوانكي؟
Come out if you dare!
اخرج إذا كنت تجرؤ!
Fine.
بخير.
It's you!
انه انت!
I'll chop you into minced meat.
سوف أقوم بتقطيعك إلى لحم مفروم.
Why are you stopping me?
لماذا توقفني؟
They are already at our door.
هم بالفعل على بابنا.
Let's kill them!
لنقتلهم!
Everyone,
الجميع،
you are just here for the Wushan.
أنت هنا فقط من أجل Wushan.
I'll give them to you.
سأعطيهم لك.
Are those the Wushan?
هل هؤلاء هم وشان؟
You just give them what they want?
أنت فقط تعطيهم ما يريدون؟
What about my dignity?
ماذا عن كرامتي؟
Wushan is not rare.
وشان ليس نادرا.
It only works to suppress
إنه يعمل فقط لقمع
my brother's demonic energy.
طاقة أخي الشيطانية.
If you want,
إذا أردت،
just take them.
فقط خذهم.
But after that,
لكن بعد ذلك ،
you must leave immediately.
يجب أن تغادر على الفور.
Don't cause any more trouble.
لا تسبب المزيد من المتاعب.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
don't blame me for being rude.
لا تلومني لكوني وقح.
The two of them
كلاهما
are good at acting.
يجيدون التمثيل.
Even I would believe these were the real Wushan.
حتى أنني كنت أعتقد أن هؤلاء كانوا وشان الحقيقي.
What?
لما؟
Wushan is an extraordinary medicine
وشان هو دواء غير عادي
and is extremely rare.
وهو نادر للغاية.
How could it be possible to
كيف يمكن أن يكون ذلك ممكنا
get a basket of it so easily?
الحصول على سلة منه بسهولة؟
They must be lying.
لا بد أنهم يكذبون.
Hand over the real Wushan.
تسليم وشان الحقيقي.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Wushan is indeed rare.
وشان نادر بالفعل.
But if you get the Wushan,
ولكن إذا حصلت على Wushan ،
how will you divide them?
كيف تقسمهم
Don't listen to her nonsense.
لا تستمع إلى هرائها.
Let's get the real Wushan first.
دعنا نحصل على Wushan الحقيقي أولاً.
Look.
نظرة.
Why are you getting so impatient?
لماذا نفد صبرك؟
You look guilty.
تبدو مذنبا.
Are you trying to
هل تحاول
to have the Wushan all to yourself?
أن يكون لديك Wushan لنفسك؟
Cut the crap. Just kill them.
قطع الفضلات.  فقط اقتلهم.
This is interesting.
هذا مثير للاهتمام.
Look.
نظرة.
The great devil is killing people.
الشيطان العظيم يقتل الناس.
Guys, let's go together.
يا رفاق ، دعنا نذهب معًا.
Kill the great devil and eliminate the hazard of the martial arts circle.
اقتل الشيطان العظيم واقضِ على خطر دائرة فنون الدفاع عن النفس.
Who are you? You can actually stabilize my brother.
من أنت؟  يمكنك في الواقع تثبيت استقرار أخي.
Physician Yan, it's you.
الطبيب يان ، هذا أنت.
Miss Tang.
ملكة جمال تانغ.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
Your disease
مرضك
hasn't recovered at all.
لم يتعافى على الإطلاق.
If you can't cure it,
إذا لم تستطع علاجه ،
then other physicians can't cure it too.
ثم لا يستطيع الأطباء الآخرون علاجه أيضًا.
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
This is Yan Ran, a miraculous physician,
هذا يان ران ، طبيب معجزة ،
also known as Yanwang Chou.
يُعرف أيضًا باسم Yanwang Chou.
He has excellent medical skills.
لديه مهارات طبية ممتازة.
If he ranks second in the world,
إذا احتل المرتبة الثانية في العالم ،
no one dares to be number one.
لا أحد يجرؤ على أن يكون رقم واحد.
Well,
نحن سوف،
don't be fooled by Physician Yan's appearance.
لا تنخدع بمظهر الطبيب يان.
Since he's a strange doctor,
بما أنه طبيب غريب
he has to be extraordinary.
يجب أن يكون غير عادي.
As long as his medical skills are good.
طالما أن مهاراته الطبية جيدة.
We only need his medical skills to be good.
نحتاج فقط إلى مهاراته الطبية لنكون جيدين.
Guys,
رفاق،
let's attack together
دعونا نهاجم معا
now that Yun Gaixue can't move.
الآن أن Yun Gaixue لا يستطيع التحرك.
Wait.
انتظر.
You always ask us to do it.
أنت تطلب منا دائمًا القيام بذلك.
Why don't you do it yourself?
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك بنفسك؟
I'm giving you the chance
أنا أعطيك الفرصة
to make a great achievement.
لتحقيق إنجاز عظيم.
We don't need it.
نحن لا نحتاجها.
I didn't expect all heroes
لم أكن أتوقع كل الأبطال
to be here.
حتى تكون هنا.
Who is this?
من هذا؟
Do you know him?
هل تعرفه؟
Li Chengtian.
لي تشنغتيان.
Why did he turn his back to us after he showed up?
لماذا أدار ظهره لنا بعد أن ظهر؟
He must be a master.
يجب أن يكون سيدًا.
Masters all look like this when they show up.
جميع الأساتذة يبدون هكذا عند ظهورهم.
Isn't he
أليس كذلك
Master Li Chengtian,
السيد لي تشنغتيان ،
the chief of Lingjue Sect, the world's strongest sect?
زعيم طائفة Lingjue ، أقوى طائفة في العالم؟
Why is he here?
لماذا هو هنا؟
Chief Li also wants the Wushan?
الزعيم لي يريد أيضا Wushan؟
Don't get me wrong.
لا تفهموني خطأ.
I'm not here for the Wushan,
أنا لست هنا من أجل Wushan ،
but to persuade
لكن للإقناع
my two nephews to turn over a new leaf.
ابني أخي لفتح صفحة جديدة.
We have nothing to do
ليس لدينا ما نفعله
with Lingjue Sect.
مع طائفة Lingjue.
Xi'er, I know
Xi'er ، أنا أعلم
you've been holding grudges
كنت تحمل ضغينة
for I taught you ancestral skills.
لأنني علمتك مهارات الأجداد.
But I only did that to teach you martial arts
لكنني فعلت ذلك فقط لأعلمك فنون الدفاع عن النفس
and help you grow up soon.
ومساعدتك على النمو قريبًا.
You betrayed Lingjue Sect.
لقد قمت بخيانة طائفة Lingjue.
Do you know how sad I am?
هل تعلم كم انا حزين؟
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
Don't you understand?
الا تفهم
The Double Demons of Xuanqi Mountain had ancestral skills passed down to them,
كان لدى الشياطين المزدوجة لجبل Xuanqi مهارات أسلاف انتقلت إليهم ،
yet they are unhappy about it.
ومع ذلك فهم غير راضين عن ذلك.
In the end, they betrayed Lingjue Sect.
في النهاية ، خانوا Lingjue Sect.
How ungrateful.
كيف جاحد.
My confidant.
صديقي.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
But now you've become possessed by demons while practicing martial arts,
لكنك الآن أصبحت ممسوسًا بالشياطين أثناء ممارستك لفنون الدفاع عن النفس ،
and are despised by all martial artists.
ومحتقر من قبل كل فناني الدفاع عن النفس.
Today, I must
اليوم ، لا بد لي
take you back and discipline you strictly.
يعيدك ويضبطك بصرامة.
I can't let you harm the martial arts circle anymore.
لا يمكنني السماح لك بإيذاء دائرة فنون الدفاع عن النفس بعد الآن.
Right?
حق؟
-Yes. -Yes.
-نعم.  -نعم.
Shut up, mister.
اخرس يا سيد.
Where did you come from?
من أين أتيت؟
When did you see them harming the martial arts circle?
متى رأيتهم يضرون بدائرة فنون الدفاع عن النفس؟
Obviously it's these people
من الواضح أنهم هؤلاء الناس
who came here to robb the Wushan.
الذي جاء إلى هنا لسرقة ووشان.
Even if they are here to rob,
حتى لو كانوا هنا للسرقة ،
you shouldn't kill them.
لا تقتلهم.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
You came up to rob the Wushan.
جئت لسرقة ووشان.
But we have to welcome you
لكن علينا أن نرحب بك
with open arms?
بصدر رحب؟
According to this logic,
وفقًا لهذا المنطق ،
I'll take some people to Lingjue Sect tomorrow.
سآخذ بعض الناس إلى Lingjue Sect غدًا.
Chief Li, please welcome us with open arms
الرئيس لي ، من فضلك رحب بنا بأذرع مفتوحة
and let us rob you.
ودعونا نسرق منك.
Ridiculous! Ridiculous!
سخيف!  سخيف!
You can make up stories,
يمكنك تأليف القصص ،
and I can't be unreasonable?
ولا يمكنني أن أكون غير معقول؟
You martial artists
أنتم فناني الدفاع عن النفس
speak of benevolence and morality all day,
نتحدث عن الإحسان والأخلاق طوال اليوم ،
but in fact, you're full of bad ideas.
لكن في الحقيقة ، أنت مليء بالأفكار السيئة.
Although Li Chengxi is cursed by you,
على الرغم من أن لي تشنغشي ملعون منك ،
I believe
أعتقد
he is not a person
هو ليس بشخص
who would betray his sect.
من يخون طائفته.
There must have been some problems with your Lingjue Sect.
لابد أنه كانت هناك بعض المشاكل مع طائفة Lingjue الخاصة بك.
You...
أنت...
Enough.
كافية.
It's more important to treat Xue now.
من المهم معالجة Xue الآن.
I'll say it again.
سأقولها مرة أخرى.
If someone makes trouble again,
إذا تسبب شخص ما في مشكلة مرة أخرى ،
he'll be just like this tree.
سيكون مثل هذه الشجرة تمامًا.
You're so stubborn.
أنت عنيد جدا.
Guys, let's stay on Xuanqi Mountain.
يا رفاق ، دعنا نبقى على جبل Xuanqi.
I don't believe we can't get the real Wushan.
لا أصدق أننا لا نستطيع الحصول على Wushan الحقيقي.
Right?
حق؟
Stay on Xuanqi Mountain.
ابق على جبل Xuanqi.
Brother,
شقيق،
we can't defeat the Double Demons of Xuanqi Mountain.
لا يمكننا هزيمة الشياطين المزدوجة لجبل Xuanqi.
Can we get the Wushan if we stay here?
هل يمكننا الحصول على Wushan إذا بقينا هنا؟
If we can't get the Wushan in the hard way,
إذا لم نتمكن من الحصول على Wushan بالطريقة الصعبة ،
we can use some tactics.
يمكننا استخدام بعض التكتيكات.
When the dark night comes...
عندما يأتي الليل المظلم ...
Stay on Xuanqi Mountain.
ابق على جبل Xuanqi.
Stay on Xuanqi Mountain!
ابق على جبل Xuanqi!
You were hit just now. Are you okay?
لقد تم ضربك الآن.  هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
With Physician Yan here,
مع الطبيب يان هنا ،
Yun Gaixue will be fine.
سيكون Yun Gaixue بخير.
When Xue was possessed before,
عندما كان Xue ممسوسًا من قبل ،
he can be suppressed by icy martial skills and Wushan.
يمكن قمعه من خلال المهارات القتالية الجليدية و Wushan.
I didn't expect it to be so serious this time.
لم أكن أتوقع أن يكون الأمر بهذه الخطورة هذه المرة.
Yun Gaixue is possessed.
يمتلك Yun Gaixue.
Chief,
رئيس،
Young Master and Shadow have started
بدأ السيد الشاب و Shadow
to practice Book of Xincan.
لممارسة كتاب Xincan.
But they are brothers after all.
لكنهم إخوة بعد كل شيء.
I'm worried that when Young Master turns 18,
أنا قلق من أنه عندما يبلغ Young Master 18 عامًا ،
he won't absorb Shadow's power.
لن يمتص قوة الظل.
This is the fate of twins.
هذا هو مصير التوائم.
No one can disobey it.
لا أحد يستطيع أن يعصيها.
Even if Xi and Xue disagree,
حتى لو اختلف Xi و Xue ،
we must do everything to force them to finish it.
يجب أن نفعل كل شيء لإجبارهم على الانتهاء منه.
Yes.
نعم.
Keep quiet.
الزم الصمت.
On the 18th birthday,
في عيد الميلاد الثامن عشر ،
[Lingjue Sect]
[طائفة لينجيو]
I didn't absorb Xue's power.
لم أستوعب قوة Xue.
So we were both possessed by demons.
لذلك كان كلانا ممسوسًا بالشياطين.
In order to get rid of the inner demon,
من أجل التخلص من الشيطان الداخلي ،
I started looking for a solution.
بدأت في البحث عن حل.
I didn't expect that the two of them
لم أكن أتوقع أن يكون الاثنان
suffered so much in the past.
عانى كثيرا في الماضي.
If it weren't for the Book of Xincan in Lingjue Sect,
إذا لم يكن من أجل كتاب Xincan في Lingjue Sect ،
they would have grown up healthily
كانوا سيكبرون بصحة جيدة
like normal kids.
مثل الاطفال العاديين.
Does the Book of Yueque work?
هل يعمل كتاب يويكي؟
Have you started practicing?
هل بدأت ممارسة؟
I'm practicing it.
أنا أمارسها.
But I'm not sure if it'll work,
لكنني لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان سيعمل ،
so I didn't dare to let Xue try.
لذلك لم أجرؤ على السماح لـ Xue بالمحاولة.
Physician Yan.
الطبيب يان.
Physician Yan, how is Xue?
دكتور يان ، كيف حال شيويه؟
Don't worry. He's fine.
لا تقلق.  انه على ما يرام.
I told you.
أخبرتك.
With Physician Yan, Yun Gaixue will be fine.
مع الطبيب يان ، سيكون يون جيكسو على ما يرام.
He is possessed by demons.
هو ممسوس بالشياطين.
His meridians are blocked.
تم حظر خطوط الطول الخاصة به.
He only has a few months to live.
لديه فقط بضعة أشهر ليعيشها.
You just said he was fine.
لقد قلت للتو أنه بخير.
Yes.
نعم.
His disease is fine.
مرضه بخير.
I've been a physician for so many years.
لقد كنت طبيبة لسنوات عديدة.
This is the first time
هذه اول مرة
I've met such a challenging disease.
لقد قابلت مثل هذا المرض الصعب.
Is there any cure?
هل يوجد علاج؟
The meridians are blocked. How can we cure them?
تم حظر خطوط الطول.  كيف نعالجهم؟
You should start preparing for the funeral.
يجب أن تبدأ في التحضير للجنازة.
If you met an ordinary physician,
إذا قابلت طبيبًا عاديًا ،
he would say that.
سيقول ذلك.
But you are lucky
لكنك محظوظ
to meet me.
لمقابلتي.
I will never send him to hell.
لن أرسله إلى الجحيم أبدًا.
Can't you finish your words at once?
ألا يمكنك إنهاء كلامك مرة واحدة؟
We were so worried.
كنا قلقين للغاية.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
show me Wushan.
أرني وشان.
Yes.
نعم.
This is the Wushan.
هذا هو وشان.
This ugly thing
هذا الشيء القبيح
is really the Wushan.
هو حقا وشان.
So you weren't acting just now?
إذن أنت لا تتصرف الآن؟
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
How could Yun Gaixue be so good at acting?
كيف يمكن أن يكون Yun Gaixue جيدًا في التمثيل؟
It does work.
انها تقوم بالعمل.
But it's not mature yet.
لكنها لم تنضج بعد.
A basket of trash.
سلة قمامة.
This is even more useless to you.
هذا حتى أكثر عديمة الفائدة بالنسبة لك.
So I came here for nothing.
لذلك جئت إلى هنا من أجل لا شيء.
No, no.
مهووس.
I'm here to help you.
أنا هنا لمساعدتك.
Physician Yan,
الطبيب يان
I'll go and ripen the Wushan.
سأذهب وتنضج Wushan.
Get more matured ones.
احصل على المزيد من النضج.
Otherwise, it won't work well.
خلاف ذلك ، لن يعمل بشكل جيد.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
I tried so hard to give you a chance,
حاولت جاهدًا أن أعطيك فرصة ،
but you got nothing.
لكنك لم تحصل على شيء.
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
Li Chengxi has been keeping the Book of Yueque with him.
ظل لي تشنغشي يحتفظ بكتاب يويكي معه.
I can't do it.
لا أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك.
It seems I have to think of another way.
يبدو أن علي التفكير بطريقة أخرى.
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Don't worry. I'm here.
لا تقلق.  أنا هنا.
Here.
هنا.
This matured Wushan really has a mind of its own.
هذا وشان الناضج لديه حقًا عقل خاص به.
Physician Yan, take a look.
الطبيب يان ، الق نظرة.
Are these enough?
هل هذه كافية؟
If not,
ان لم،
I can make more.
يمكنني صنع المزيد.
Okay. Put them down here.
تمام.  ضعهم هنا.
I haven't figured out how to cure him.
لم أفهم كيفية علاجه.
I heard that the Book of Yueque works.
سمعت أن كتاب يويكي يعمل.
However,
لكن،
I'm not sure if I can get rid of the demonic energy.
لست متأكدًا مما إذا كان بإمكاني التخلص من الطاقة الشيطانية.
I've practiced a part of it.
لقد مارست جزءًا منها.
But I haven't figured out the last move.
لكنني لم أحسب الخطوة الأخيرة.
The last move?
الخطوة الأخيرة؟
[Secret of Kungfu]
[سر الكونغفو]
Only the one you fall in love with
فقط الشخص الذي تقع في حبه
can help you practice this skill.
يمكن أن تساعدك في ممارسة هذه المهارة.
Give me your hand.
اعطني يدك.
I can't feel anything with your pulse.
لا أشعر بأي شيء بنبضك.
When do you usually get possessed?
متى عادة ما تصاب بالمس؟
The property of my martial skills
خاصية مهارات الدفاع عن النفس
helps me to control the demonic energy more easily.
يساعدني على التحكم في الطاقة الشيطانية بسهولة أكبر.
It nearly broke out several times.
كادت أن تندلع عدة مرات.
It seems that
يبدو أن
they all have something to do with
كل منهم له علاقة
being in close physical contact with Miss Tang.
كونها على اتصال جسدي وثيق مع الآنسة تانغ.
I didn't expect you to be such a pervert.
لم أكن أتوقع أن تكون مثل هذا المنحرف.
Do you get possessed
هل تمس
when touching other women too?
عند لمس النساء الأخريات أيضًا؟
I've never had close contact with other women.
لم يكن لدي اتصال وثيق مع نساء أخريات.
So,
لذا،
you're easily possessed
كنت ممسوسًا بسهولة
once you have close contact with women.
بمجرد أن يكون لديك اتصال وثيق مع النساء.
That's easy.
هذا سهل.
Just find a random woman and try it.
فقط ابحث عن امرأة عشوائية وجربها.
Are you still...
هل ما زلت...
I didn't expect the chief of Xuanqi Mountain
لم أكن أتوقع رئيس جبل Xuanqi
to still be a virgin.
أن تظل عذراء.
If you don't have a suitable candidate,
إذا لم يكن لديك مرشح مناسب ،
why don't you go to the brothel in the city?
لماذا لا تذهب الى بيت الدعارة في المدينة؟
That's not necessary.
هذا ليس ضروريا.
Sugar cake.
كعكة السكر.
Don't take my sugar cake. Stop there.
لا تأخذ كعكة السكر الخاصة بي.  توقف هناك.
This guy...
هذا الشخص...
is he the reincarnation of a starving ghost?
هل هو تناسخ شبح جائع؟
He doesn't forget to eat even when he's sick.
لا ينسى أن يأكل حتى عندما يكون مريضًا.
What? Why are you hesitating?
لما؟  لماذا انت متردد؟
Don't you want to cure your brother?
ألا تريد أن تعالج أخيك؟
Physician Yan,
الطبيب يان
I'll leave Xue to you.
سأترك Xue لك.
I...
أنا...
I'll try it.
سأحاول ذلك.
By the way,
بالمناسبة،
remember to try a few more times
تذكر أن تحاول عدة مرات
to ensure your success.
لضمان نجاحك.
You mean
أنت تعني
you want to test the demonic energy
تريد اختبار الطاقة الشيطانية
through intimate contact with me?
من خلال الاتصال الحميم معي؟
Physician Yan said so.
قال الطبيب يان ذلك.
If you feel uncomfortable,
إذا كنت تشعر بعدم الارتياح ،
you can reject it.
يمكنك رفضه.
It's okay.
انه بخير.
It's for curing your demonic energy anyway.
إنه لعلاج طاقتك الشيطانية على أي حال.
You helped me a lot in the Tang Sect.
لقد ساعدتني كثيرًا في طائفة تانغ.
I should help you.
يجب أن أساعدك.
But
لكن
what should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Like this?
مثله؟
You...
أنت...
can you let go of me first?
هل يمكنك تركني اولا
What's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
Is this not close enough?
أليس هذا قريبًا بما يكفي؟
What else should we try?
ماذا يجب ان نحاول ايضا؟
The Book of Yueque is about martial skills.
يدور كتاب يويك حول المهارات القتالية.
Why don't we practice it together?
لماذا لا نمارسها معًا؟
Practice?
ممارسة؟
How?
كيف؟
Watch me.
راقبني.
How is it, Li Chengxi?
كيف الحال يا لي تشنغسي؟
Were you possessed just now?
هل كنت ممسوسًا الآن؟
Your eyes didn't turn blue.
عيناك لم تتحول إلى اللون الأزرق.
That means it worked.
هذا يعني أنها عملت.
Maybe, we're
ربما نحن
not intimate enough.
ليس حميميا بما فيه الكفاية.
It's possible.
انه ممكن.
I have a book with some movements
لدي كتاب مع بعض الحركات
that we can try.
يمكننا أن نحاول.
Look.
نظرة.
This...
هذه...
[×ography Writer——I won't tell you -Get on the horse]
[× كاتب ography—— لن أخبرك - اصعد على الحصان]
Where did you get this?
من اين حصلت على هذا؟
It was in between Zhi's dialogue novel.
كان بين رواية حوار Zhi.
He read it secretly, so I confiscated it.
قرأها سرا فصادرتها.
No.
رقم.
It's inappropriate.
إنه غير ملائم.
Why is it inappropriate? I think some...
لماذا هو غير مناسب؟  أعتقد بعض ...
No.
رقم.
Yes.
نعم.
Just take a look.
فقط الق نظرة.
No.
رقم.
Li Chengxi.
لي تشنغسي.
Your eyes are turning blue.
عيونك تتحول إلى اللون الأزرق.